

Jude I Ndubuisi

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



Address

Al Roda Tower One Al Nahda Dubai United Arab Emirates

Phone Number +971522723497

Website

https://judendubuisi.netlify.app/

Email Address

ikechukwujudendubuisi@gmail.co

m

Github

CodeJude

Twitter

JudeVector

LinkedIn

Jude Ndubuisi

Instagram

Judevector

TOOLS AND TECHNOLOGIES

HTML CSS

React Javascript
Python Nodejs

MongoDB Git

Bootstrap

CERTIFICATIONS

Mechanical Engineering National Diploma

Federal Polytechnic Oko

The Complete Web Development Bootcamp

Udemy

LANGUAGES

English Igbo Superior Native

HOBBIES

Mindfulness

Travelling

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a solution-driven Entry-level Web Developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, React and JavaScript. also knowledgeable in Nodejs and Mongodb, Built products for desktop and mobile app users, meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices and speed. Designed and developed web applications across multiple APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tale-Hub Builders
Junior Front End Developer

(September 2022 - Present)

Performed user experience quality assurance testing to identify and remedy shortcomings.

- Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements.
- Coded using HTML, CSS and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.
- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
- Tested web-based product functionality and delivered iterations to customer.

Freelancer

Frontend Developer

(November 2021 - Present)

- Coded using HTML, CSS and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.
- Advocated for well-tested and documented, high quality code.
- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
- Followed SDLC best practices within Agile environment to produce rapid iterations for clients.
- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications

EDUCATION

Federal Polytechnic Oko Mechanical Engineering

(November 2016 - June 2018)

SKILLS

Team Leading, Problem solving, Critical thinking

Research, Reporting, Project

management

PROJECTS

Personal Portfolio

https://judendubuisi.netlify.app/

- Built my personal portfolio using React and material UI
- Used Framer motion for motion in styling it
- Used the best practices in writing React

Note App

https://vectorsnoteapp.netlify.app/

• Built a note app for daily note taking *Used React for its functionality

Ecommerce Site

- Currently building a full MERN ecommerce site using React
- Nodejs is used for its server side *Mongodb will be used for its database

Swimming Photography